Guide to the Cornell University Track and Field collection, ca. 1886-2000
Cornell University Track and Field collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Track and Field collection, ca. 1886-2000
40-9-1820
Cornell University
8 cu. ft.
Manuscripts, Photographs, Films
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Materials documenting the history of the track teams at Cornell.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Materials documenting the history of the track teams at Cornell. Collection contains a collection of training logs and results books as well as various programs and ephemera relating to events and operations of the track team. Many photos and slides of individual team members and events, some photos include trips to England. A collection of medals won by Walker Smith is included as well as another set won by Daniel B. Strickler. Material from Los Angeles, Antwerp, Berlin and Oslo Summer Olympic Games material from Cornell Olympians including film footage and photos. Winning jersey bib number plates worn by winners in track and field at the 1920 Antwerp Belgium Olympics, this includes non-U.S. and non-Cornell winners as well, some are signed. Many films of various track events and training sessions. Films include, but are not limited to: IC4A and Heptagonal track and field events, 1932; Penn Relays, 1955; 1952 Olympics. Also a film primarily concerning Cornell athletics, including track and field and baseball that includes Spring Day games, a parade, male students clowning, and the Green Dragon. Also pictorial log of the trip to England of the track teams of Cornell University and Princeton University. The album has photographs, clippings, and memorabilia documenting the Anglo-American Athletic Match track and field events held in England between Cornell and Princeton and Oxford and Cambridge in July 1930. Also programs from the Niagara Track & Field Hall of Fame, featuring Cornellians.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bannister, Roger; Foss, Frank; Gourdine, Meredith; Moakley, John F.; Treman, Charles E., Jr.; Cambridge University -- Track athletics.; Cornell University -- Athletics.; Cornell University -- Baseball.; Cornell University -- Track athletics.; Cornell University -- Students.; Green Dragon (Cornell University); Oxford University -- Track athletics.; Princeton University -- Track athletics.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Walter Ashbaugh '51, Meredith Gourdine '52 and Charles H. Moore '51 competed at the 52 Olympics and may be featured on the film.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also the Hunt Bradley papers, #41-2-1550, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA01550
SERIES LIST
Series I. General papers, photographs and ephemera
Box 1, 7, 9, 10, Mapcase
Series II. Training and Results Books
Box 2-3
Series III. Oversize Photographs
Box 4-6, Mapcase
Series IV. Videos and Film
Box 7-8
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. General papers, photographs, and ephemera
  - Field day NYSIAU, 1886, 93, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photos, 1900-09 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 1900s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Track Photos, 1910-19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NY state intercollegiate Track and Field meet. Rome, NY, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Track Photos, 1920-29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    One photo features many of the track coach contemporaries of Jack Moakley at an event. Also includes program from the March 24, 1923 Michigan Dual Meet.
  - Disassembled collage featuring the number plates worn by track and field athletes on their jerseys at the 1920 Olympics in Antwerp Belgium who won gold medals. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Several of the number plates are autographed by the athletes. The plates include Frank Foss, (Cornell '17) signed, Joseph Guillemot, Albert Hill signed (also appears signed by Horace Hallock Brown, Hannes Kolehmainen, Richmond Landon signed, Frank Loomis signed (also signed by Frank Sheehan Cornell trainer, Pat McDonald signed, Charley Paddock, Bevil Rudd, Patrick Ryan signed, and Earl Thomson. The one for Allen Woodring is missing. There are also two that have name labels that do not correspond with who won gold. They are shot put labeled "Finnthuma" actually won by Ville Pörhölä and broad jump labeled "Finna" actually won by William Petersson.
    Also includes a picture of Jack Moakley and Frank Sheehan and a U.S. Olympic track team patch. See photo on CD-1941 (located in Box 1, as well) for picture before it was disassembled.
  - Pieces of the 1920 Olympic collage from folder 8. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Track Photos, 1930-39 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Berlin Olympics programs, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Berlin Olympics, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tickets to Berlin Olympics, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Track Photos, 1940-49 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Includes negatives of what appear to be the IC4A and English meets of 1949. Also slides of the 1949 English meet and training slides of shot put showing technique at all stages of the throw and other 1949 slides.
  - Cornell Spiked Shoe Society, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Track Photos, 1950-59 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Some of the prints come from a film can of negatives in folder 1-44. They include photos of Meredith Gourdine.
  - Track Photos, ca. 1952 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Film cannister of negatives. Some of the prints from this can are in an envelope in folder 1-16. They include photos of Meredith Gourdine.
  - Projector photograph slides of the 1950 England trip (Box 1, Folder 16)
    With Cornell and Princeton track teams for matches against Cambridge and Oxford. Includes photos of the matches, but also photos of the ships they traveled on, various landmarks, stops in Paris, climbing the Eiffel Tower, Luxembourg Gardens, Statue of Liberty. Roger Bannister would compete at one of the events.
  - Charles Moore Jr., winner of a gold and silver medal, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1952 Oslo Olympics (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Track Photos, 1960-69 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Track Photos, 1970-79 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Includes some slides.
  - The Midwest Olympic Development Camp, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Track Photos, 1980-89 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Inside Track: Creating Success at Cornell, by Colin McClive, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Men's and Women's Workout Notebook (blank), 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - University of Missouri Summer Camp, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, Jan 31 - Feb 1 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - University of Missouri XC and Track and Field Camp, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Marines Article, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - University of Missouri XC and Track and Field Camp, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - University of Missouri XC and Track and Field Camp, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - University of Missouri Speed Development Camp, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Track Photos, 1990's (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - University of Missouri XC and Track and Field Camp, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - University of Missouri Coaches Clinic, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - H. Hunt Bradley Track Center Dedication, Feb 25, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Track and Field News's Big Red Book, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Track Photos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Training Manual, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Minnesota Women's Training Diary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - CD-1941, contains low resolution photographs of many of the photos in the collection when they were on the wall in Barton Hall track room, before they were unframed. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Niagara Track & Field Hall of Fame programs and tickets, 1998-2014 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Includes list of Cornellians in the Hall of Fame
  - Niagara Track & Field Hall of Fame programs, 2012-2014 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - University College Dublin Athletic Club Visit to Cornell University plaque, April 1983 (Box 7)
  - University of Birmingham and Kingston Upon Hull plaques (Box 7)
  - Anglo-American Athletic Match Scrapbook, 1930 (Box 9)
    "A pictorial log of the trip to England of the track teams of Cornell University and Princeton University." The album has photographs, clippings, and memorabilia documenting the Anglo-American Athletic Match track and field events held in England between Cornell and Princeton and Oxford and Cambridge in July 1930.
  - Glass plate negative of 2 Cornell runners - Henry Norton Stone and Frederic Kimball Lovejoy, ca. 1900's (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Programs from the 1930 England trip, July 12, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photos from the 1934 and 1938 England trip, 1934, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Varsity track wearer of the C certificate of Clarence Francis Spindler, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Photos and ephemera from the 1930 England trip (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Includes letter from Princeton's Alfred Mills to Cornell's Carl Henry Meinig mentioning the trip and a newsclipping from The Illustrated and Sporting Dramatic News, July 19, 1930.
  - Track medals won by Walker Smith '20, 1918-1920 (Box 10)
    32 medals removed from mounting on a board. The medals are from a number of different competitions including, the Amateur Athletic Union of the United States, Svensk Amerikanska, IC4A, Meadowbrook Club of Philadelphia, Achilles Club of Britain, Queens Club of London, Boston Athletic Association, New York Athletic Club, Harvard, Yale, 1920 Olympics in Antwerp Belgium medal presented by John Hylan, mayor of New York and others.
  - Track medals won by Daniel Strickler '22, 1921-1922 (Box 10)
    3 medals, one for the 1 mile run at the Indoor Triangular Meet 1922 with Cornell, Dartmouth, Harvard meet, one from the International Track & Field Meet on Travers Island with Oxford, Cambridge, Princeton, Cornell meet and one a medallion with an image of runners on it..
  - Wood frame engraved with former runners initials., Wood Frame
    A photo of Jack Moakley in front of a very similar, but different wood frame can be seen in Box 1 folder 41.
- Series II. Training and Results Books
  - Cornell Cross-Country Club, October 1898-1925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - IC4A 33rd Annual Field Meeting, Franklin Field, Philadelphia PA, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - IC4A 34th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - IC4A 35th Annual Field Meeting, Franklin Field, Philadelphia PA, 1910 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - IC4A 36th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - IC4A 37th Annual Field Meeting, Franklin Field, Philadelphia PA, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - IC4A 38th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - IC4A 39th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cross country summary for the year, 1914-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Track Summary, 1914-15 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - IC4A 40th Annual Field Meeting, Franklin Field, Philadelphia PA, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Business Management of the Cornell Track Team, Paul F Sanborne, Manager, 1915-16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - IC4A 41st annual field meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Track Summary, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Track Summary, 1919-20 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Track Summary, 1920-21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Track Reports, 1921-22 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Track Charles Crawford Carter, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - IC4A 46th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Track Report, 1922-23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Track Schedules and Reports, 1923-24 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Track Schedules and Reports, 1923-24 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cross Country Reports, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cross Country Reports, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Track Schedules and Reports, 1924-25 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Track Schedules and Reports, 1924-25 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Track Schedules and Reports, 1925-26 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - IC4A 50th Annual Field Meeting, Soldiers Field, Cambridge MA, May 28-28, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - IC4A Souvenir Volume of Annual Championship Meetings, 1927-28 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Track Records and Schedules, 1928-29 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - IC4A Souvenir Volume of Annual Championship Meetings, 1929-32 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - IC4A Souvenir Volume of Annual Championship Meetings, 1929-32 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - IC4A Souvenir Volume of Annual Championship Meetings, 1929-32 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Series III. Oversize Photographs
  - 1890's
    - Partial Photo of the Track Team, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1900's
    - Photo of the Track Team, 1902-03 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Photo of the Track Team, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Photo of the Track Team, 1906-07 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1920's
    - Track Team Photo, 1922-23 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Track Team Photo, 1928-29 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1930's
    - Track Team Photo, 1930-31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Track Team Photo - in 2 pieces, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Track Team Photo, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Single runner, unknown, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1940's
    - Track Team Photo, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Track Team Photo, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Coach Moakley, retired in 1949, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1970's
    - Ithaca Journal, Cornell wins Heps, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1980's
    - Cornell Hall of Fame Induction, George Miske, class of 1922, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Hall of Fame Induction, Alma M Richards, class of 1917, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1990's
    - Cornell Hall of Fame Induction, Robert E Brown, class of 1922, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Undated Photo
    - Track Team photo, plus four individual photos, Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Photographs, No Date (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - General Photographs, 1900-09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General Photographs, 1910-19 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General Photographs, 1920-29 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - General Photographs, 1930-39 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - General Photographs, 1950-59 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - General Photographs, 1960-69 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Signs and posters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Includes things like the 1944-45 11th Annual Heptagonal Championship poster
  - Oversize photographs, 1970-99 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Oversize photographs, 1940-59 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Oversize photographs, 1930-39 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Oversize photographs, 1920-29 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Oversize photographs, 1900-19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Oversize photographs, 1880-99 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Oversize photographs, No Date (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Large Team Individual Photograph, No Date (Map-case Folder)
  - Large Cornell, Yale, Harvard, Navy Princeton, West Point, Dartmouth group photo, No Date (Map-case Folder)
- Series IV. Videos and Film
  - Track and Field motion picture film (1 reel, 16mm), 1925; F-152 (Box 8)
    Most footage for track and field events Also Includes: male students clowning, Spring Day games such as "Ring a duck" and "Nigger in a tub" Parade with floats (one, "Dean of Ithaca" truck) and the Dragon Field and track training and competition Baseball
  - The Cornell-Princeton Track meet, May 25, 1929; F-509 (Box 7)
  - Track IC4A Philly, 1929; F-510 (Box 7)
  - Princeton-Dartmouth Pennsylvania-Cornell Track meet, 1929; F-511 (Box 7)
  - English Meet, 1930; F-512 (Box 7)
    Good enough for a showing
  - Distance events, 1932; F-513 (Box 7)
    Including 1932 Olympics in Los Angeles
  - Field Events IC4A, 1932; F-602 (Box 8)
  - Running Events IC4A, July 1-2, 1932; F-1071 (Box 8)
    University of California Berkeley, Edwards Field
  - English Meet Reel I, 1934; F-514 (Box 7)
  - English Meet Reel II, 1934; F-515 (Box 7)
  - Reel I, 1937; F-516 (Box 7)
  - Reel II, 1937; F-517 (Box 7)
  - English Trip, 1938; F-518 (Box 7)
  - Cornell Penn Relays, 1938; F-519 (Box 7)
  - Indoor Heps, Boston, 1949 and 1953; F-520 (Box 7)
  - English Trip Reel I, 1950; F-521 (Box 7)
    This film is in poor condition and may no longer be playable.
  - English Trip Reel II, 1950; F-522 (Box 7)
  - English Trip Reel III, 1950; F-523 (Box 7)
  - Trip 2, 1950; F-524 (Box 7)
  - Penn Relay Duplicate, 880 yard Relay, 1950; F-525 (Box 7A)
  - 400 M Hurdles, Olympics, 1950,51,54; F-526 (Box 7)
  - Penn Relays, 1950; F-527 (Box 7)
  - Penn Relays, 1951; F-528 (Box 7)
  - Olympics, 1952; F-603 (Box 8)
    May include film of Walter Ashbaugh '51, 4th in triple jump, Meredith Gourdine '53, Silver in long jump, Charles H Moore, Silver in relay and gold in hurdles
  - Cornell Hammer, Track Film, April 18 1954; F-529 (Box 7A)
  - Bannister Mile, 1954; F-530 (Box 7)
    Possibly footage of Roger Bannister breaking the four minute mile
  - Cross Country Season under Coach Montgomery, 1954; F-531 (Box 7)
  - Pole Vault, 1954; F-589 (Box 8B)
    Includes detailed description of each competitors technique on separate papers
  - English Trip, Oxford Cam, 1954; F-532 (Box 8)
  - Princeton Track, 1955; F-533 (Box 7)
  - Penn Relays #1, 1955; F-600 (Box 8)
  - Penn Relays Reel II, 1955; F-534 (Box 8)
  - Full Reel, Cross Country, 1955-58-60-63; F-535 (Box 8)
  - Harvard-Penn Cornell, 1956; F-536 (Box 8)
  - Penn Relays, 1956; F-537 (Box 7)
  - Belan Court and Informal Photos of Runners on Board Track, 1954; F-538 (Box 8B)
  - Colgate, 1958; F-539 (Box 7A)
  - Practice, Fort Lee, 1960; F-540 (Box 7A)
  - Cornell Track Rally, Fort Lee. Meet day, 2, 1960; F-541 (Box 7A)
  - Cornell Colgate track meet, March 25, 1960; F-542 (Box 7A)
  - Lou Montgomery, coach, includes practices of high jump and pole vault, 1961; F-543 (Box 7A)
  - Cornell Races, Mikulina-Potter, Murray-Potter, Brennan-Schenker, Feb 28 1961; F-544 (Box 7A)
  - Indoor Heps, 1961; F-575 (Box 8)
  - IC4A Track and Field at Randall's Island NY, June 25 1961; F-563 (Box 8)
  - Dartmouth Heps, Coach Montgomery, 1962; F-545 (Box 7A)
  - Cornell Track, Henson, 1962; F-546 (Box 7B)
  - Fort Lee, half of the reel is good, 1962; F-547 (Box 7B)
  - 35-SP-PV-117, 1962; F-565 (Box 8A)
  - Mikulina competing in London, High Jump 6'2-6'4, 1962; F-564 (Box 8A)
  - 3 Cornell runners: Robinowitz, Sims, Smith, March 20, 1963; F-548 (Box 7B)
  - Cornell indoor practice, Decemder 1, 1965; F-549 (Box 7B)
  - Cornell outdoor practice, includes shot-put, discus, hammer, May 26, 1965; F-550 (Box 7B)
  - Track Pole vault, February 1965; F-551 (Box 7B)
  - Practices, March 1966; F-552 (Box 7B)
  - Outdoor Track, HJ Thomas, May 1966; F-553 (Box 7B)
  - Pole vault and hurdles, Elliot and Herman, December 3, 1966; F-554 (Box 7C)
  - Track Intrasquad meet, December 11, 1966; F-555 (Box 7C)
  - Track, December 1966; F-579 (Box 8A)
  - Track Shotput, 1966; F-566 (Box 8A)
  - Track, June 1968; F-556 (Box 8B)
  - Indoor Heps, Cornell Track, 1968; F-557 (Box 7C)
  - Practice, 1968; F-558 (Box 7C)
  - Workout Practice, Feb 19-26 1968; F-559 (Box 7C)
  - W.T TRNG, 1968; F-560 (Box 7C)
  - Workout, Jan 23 1968; F-561 (Box 7C)
  - Track, Dec 1968; F-562 (Box 7C)
  - Tom Pagani, Asst Track Coach, 1970; F-568 (Box 8A)
  - Track, January 1971; F-580 (Box 8A)
  - Barton Hall, Syracuse, 1972; F-567 (Box 8A)
  - Shot Put Update, 1975; F-604 (Box 8B)
  - Hammer, January 1980; F-663 (Box 8B)
  - Lifting, 1983; F-664 (Box 8B)
  - Cornell Relays Women's Shot, December 1983; F-665 (Box 8B)
  - Long Jump, No Date, ca. 1980; F-666 (Box 8B)
  - 3 Throws, Mo Date, ca. 1980; F-667 (Box 8B)
  - Hammer #1, No Date; F-569 (Box 8)
  - Practice, photos, personalities, No Date; F-570 (Box 8)
  - Pole Vault #2, No Date; F-571 (Box 8)
  - Discus #1, No Date; F-572 (Box 8)
  - Cornell, Yale, Navy Relays, No Date; F-573 (Box 8)
  - Winter Training Hurdles, Spear, No Date; F-574 (Box 8)
  - Broad Jump Practices, No Date; F-576 (Box 8)
  - Jack Moakley, Silent, No Date; F-577 (Box 8)
  - Cornell-Princeton before sheet hurdles, No Date; F-578 (Box 8)
  - Low hurdles, odd shots. G.H. Hart, Coach Montgomery, No Date; F-581 (Box 8A)
  - Pole Vault #1, No Date; F-582 (Box 8)
  - High Hurdles, No Date; F-583 (Box 8)
  - Old Cross Country scenes #1, No Date; F-584 (Box 8)
  - Track meet, No Date; F-585 (Box 8)
  - Track, no descriptive information, No Date; F-586 (Box 8A)
  - Cornell Meet, No Date; F-587 (Box 7B)
  - Track, with sound, No Date; F-588 (Box 7C)
  - Sprints, No Date; F-590 (Box 8)
  - High Jump, No Date; F-591 (Box 8)
  - Shot, No Date; F-592 (Box 8)
  - Track, No Date; F-593 (Box 8B)
  - Track, No Date; F-594 (Box 8B)
  - Shot Weight 600, No Date; F-595 (Box 8B)
  - M9 Triple Jump Jozef Schmidt, No Date; F-596 (Box 8B)
  - K-29 High Jump Valeriy Brumel, No Date; F-597 (Box 8B)
  - Pole Vault John Pennel, 37/63, No Date; F-598 (Box 8B)
  - Discus Al Oerter P14, No Date; F-599 (Box 8B)
  - Long Jump Bob Beamon, No Date; F-668 (Box 8B)
  - Hammer Jozsef Csermak, No Date; F-669 (Box 8B)